19th and 20th century Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- France (Box 37)
  - Cities (Box 40)
    - Marignane (Box 42)
    - Marseille (Box 42)
      - Churches (Box 42)
      - Apartments-Houses (Box 43)
        - Unite d'Habitation (Box 43)
      - Plans, Sections, Models, Etc. (Box 43)
      - Exterior (Box 43)
      - Interior (Box 43)
      - Palaces (Box 43)
    - Martigues (Box 43)
    - Mathes (Box 43)
    - Montmagny (Box 43)
    - Moulins (Box 43)
    - Nancy (Box 44)
    - Nantes (Box 44)
    - Neuilly (Box 44)
      - Jaoul Houses (Box 44)
    - Nice (Box 44)
    - Nimes (Box 44)
    - Noisel-Sur-Marne (Box 44)
    - Noyon (Box 44)
    - Orly (Box 44)
    - Paris [Boxes 44-54] (Box 44)
      - Plans (Box 44)
        - 19th century Maps (Box 44)
        - Map of 1850 (Box 44)
        - 20th century Maps (Box 44)
      - Planning (Box 44)
      - General Views (Box 44)
        - Air Views (Box 44)
        - Ile de la Cite (Box 45)
        - Seine (Box 45)
        - Streets (Box 45)
      - Arches (Box 45)
        - Arc de Triomphe de L'Etoile (Box 45)
          - Arc de Triomphe du Carrousel (Box 45)
      - Banks (Box 45)
        - Bouse (Box 45)
      - Bridges (Box 45)
      - Canals (Box 45)
      - Cemeteries (Box 45)
      - Churches (Box 45)
        - Expiatory Chapel of Louis XVI (Box 45)
        - Votive Church of Joanne D'Arch (Box 45)
        - La Madeleine (Box 46)
        - La Trinite (Box 46)
        - Notre Dame De Lorette (Box 46)
        - Sacre-Coeur de Montmartre (Box 46)
        - S. Agustin (Box 46)
        - S. Clotilde (Box 46)
        - S. Spirit (Box 46)
        - S. Jean de Montmartre (Box 46)
        - S. Pierre de Montmartre (Box 46)
        - S. Roch (Box 46)
        - S. Vincent De Paul (Box 46)
      - Expositions (Box 46)
        - Exposition 1834 (Box 46)
        - Exposition 1855 (Box 46)
        - Universal Exposition 1867 (Box 46)
        - Exposition 1878 (Box 47)
          - Trocadero (Box 47)
        - International Exposition 1889 (Box 47)
          - Galerie Des Machines (Box 47)
          - Eiffel Tower (Box 47)
        - Exposition Universelle, 1900 (Box 47)
          - Grand Palais (Box 48)
          - Petit Palais (Box 48)
        - Arts Decoratifs, 1925 (Box 48)
          - Palace of Crafts (Box 48)
          - Pavilions (Box 48)
            - Collector (Box 48)
            - Pavilion l'Esprit Nouveau (Box 48)
            - Magasin (Box 48)
            - Nancy (Box 48)
            - Sevres (Box 48)
          - Foreign Pavilions (Box 48)
            - Austria (Box 48)
            - Czechoslovakia (Box 48)
            - Great Britain (Box 48)
            - Holland (Box 48)
            - Poland (Box 48)
            - Sweden (Box 48)
          - Theater (Box 49)
        - Colonial Exposition, 1931 (Box 49)
        - International Exposition, 1937 (Box 49)
          - Plans & General Views (Box 49)
          - Centre Regional (Box 49)
          - Pavilions (Box 49)
          - Foreign Pavilions (Box 49)
            - Belgium (Box 49)
            - Czechoslovakia (Box 49)
            - Finnish (Box 49)
            - Germany (Box 49)
            - Italy (Box 49)
            - Soviet Russia (Box 49)
            - Spain (Box 49)
            - Trocadero (Box 49)
      - Fountains (Box 49)
      - Garages (Box 49)
      - Government Buildings (Box 49)
        - Ministry of Finance (Box 49)
        - Ministry of Foreign Affairs (Box 49)
        - Municipal Office of 10th District (Box 49)
        - Palais Bourbon (Chamber Des Deputes) (Box 49)
        - Palais De la Chambre De Paris (Box 49)
        - Palais du Conseil D'Etat ET de la Cour Des Comptes (Box 49)
        - Palais Du Luxembourg (Box 49)
        - Post Office (Box 49)
        - Stamp Office (Box 50)
        - UNESCO Building (Box 50)
      - Hospitals (Box 50)
      - Hotels (Box 50)
        - Hotel De Bourrienne (Box 50)
        - Hotel Beauharhais (Box 50)
        - Hotel Du Figaro (Box 50)
        - Hotel George V (Box 50)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 50)
        - Various (Box 50)
        - Ozenfant House (Le Corbusier) (Box 50)
        - Tristan Tzara House (Box 50)
        - Weekend House (Le Corbusier) (Box 50)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 50)
        - Beistegui Apartments (Box 51)
        - Le Porte Molitos (Box 51)
        - 25 Rue Franklin, Perret, Arch (Box 51)
        - Rue Raynourd Apartments (Box 51)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 51)
      - Libraries (Box 51)
        - Bibliotheque Nationale (Box 51)
        - Bibliotheque S. Genevieve (Box 51)
      - Monuments (Box 51)
      - Museums (Box 51)
        - Louvre (Box 51)
          - Exterior (Box 51)
            - Seine (South) Side (Box 51)
            - Rue de Rivoli (North) Side (Box 51)
          - Interior (Box 51)
        - Modern Art Museum (Box 51)
        - Museum of Public Work (Box 51)
      - Office Buildings (Box 52)
        - Salvation Army Headquarters (Box 52)
      - Parks (Box 52)
      - Prisons (Box 52)
      - Restaurants (Box 52)
      - Schools (Box 52)
        - Ercole Des Beaux Art (Box 52)
        - University City (Box 52)
          - International Pavilion (Box 52)
          - Swiss Pavilion (Box 52)
          - New Sorbonne (Box 52)
      - Squares (Box 52)
        - Place De La Bastille (Box 52)
        - Place de la Concorde (Box 52)
      - Stations (Box 52)
        - Gare de l'Est (Box 52)
        - Gare De Lyons (Box 52)
        - Gare Du Nord (Box 52)
        - Gare D'Orleans (Box 53)
        - Gare Du Quai D'Orsay (Box 53)
        - Gare S. Lazare (Box 53)
        - Metro Stations (Box 53)
      - Stores (Box 53)
        - Various (Box 53)
        - Au Bon Marche (Box 53)
        - Central Market (Box 53)
        - Galerie D'Orleans (Box 53)
        - Maisons De Rapport (Box 53)
        - Le Mobilier National (Box 53)
        - Du Printemps (Box 53)
        - S. Germain Market (Box 53)
        - Samaritaine (Box 53)
      - Theaters (Box 53)
        - Various (Box 53)
        - Humbert De Romans (Box 53)
        - L'Opera (Box 54)
          - Exterior (Box 54)
          - Interior (Box 54)
        - Theater Des Champs-Elysees (Box 54)
        - Theater Francais (Box 54)
      - Tombs (Box 54)
      - Zoos (Box 54)
    - Pessac (Box 54)
    - Plessis-Robinson (Box 54)
    - Possy-sur-Seine (Box 54)
    - Puteaux (Box 54)
    - Puy (Box 54)
    - Raincy (Box 54)
    - Ramboucourt (Box 54)
    - Rennes (Box 54)
    - Rheims (Box 54)
      - Railroad Station (Box 54)
      - Stores (Box 54)
        - Le Halles (Box 54)
    - Rochefort (Box 54)
    - Ronchamp (Box 55)
      - Exterior (Box 55)
      - Interior (Box 55)
    - Robaix (Box 55)
    - Rouen (Box 55)
    - Roquebrune Cap Martin (Box 55)
    - Royan (Box 55)
    - S. Baume (Box 55)
    - S. Brieuc (Box 55)
    - S. Lo (Box 55)
    - S. Malo (Box 55)
    - S. Vaury (Box 55)
    - Sainte-Macaire (Box 55)
    - Sausheim (Box 55)
    - Sens (Box 55)
    - Roquebrune (Box 55)
    - Strassbourg (Box 55)
    - Tosny (Box 55)
    - Toulouse (Box 55)
    - Tours (Box 55)
      - Various (Box 55)
      - Court House (Box 55)
    - Trouville (Box 55)
    - Vaucresson (Box 55)
    - Vence (Box 56)
    - Versailles (Box 56)
    - Virchy (Box 56)
    - Vierzon (Box 56)
    - Villejuif (Box 56)
    - Ville d'Avray (Box 56)
    - Villeurbanne (Box 56)
- Germany (Box 56)
  [Boxes 56-68]
  - General Churches (Box 56)
  - General Interiors (Box 56)
  - Architects (Box 56)
    - Bartning, Otto (Box 56)
    - De Freis, H. (Box 56)
    - Endell, Auguste (Box 56)
    - Gropius, Walter (Box 56)
    - Haring, Hans (Box 56)
    - Haring, Hugo (Box 57)
    - Hoger, F. (Box 57)
    - Krois, Wilhelm (Box 57)
    - Luckhardt, Wassily (Box 57)
    - Mendelsohn, Erich (Box 57)
    - Mies van der Rohe (Box 57)
      - Brick Country House, 1923 (Box 57)
      - Drive-in Restaurant (Box 57)
      - Chicago Convention Hall, 1953 (Box 57)
      - Glass Skycraper, 1919 (Box 57)
      - Hubbe House, 1935 (Box 57)
      - Museum for Small City, 1942 (Box 57)
      - Reichsbank, 1933 (Box 57)
    - Poelzig, Hans (Box 57)
    - Scharoun, Hans (Box 57)
    - Schinkel, K.F., 1781-1841 (Box 57)
    - Schroder, P. (Box 57)
    - Schwartz, Rudof (Box 57)
    - Semper, Gottfried (Box 57)
    - Taut, Bruno (Box 58)
    - Zanth, L. von (Box 58)
  - Cities (Box 58)
    - Aachen (Box 58)
    - Aldenbere (Box 58)
    - Alfeld an der Leine (Box 58)
    - Altona (Box 58)
    - Annaberg (Box 58)
    - Augsburg (Box 58)
    - Auschwitz (Box 58)
    - Bad Homburg V.D. Home (Box 58)
    - Bamberg (Box 58)
    - Bayreuth (Box 58)
    - Berlin (Box 58)
      - Banks (Box 58)
      - Churches (Box 58)
        - Cathedral (Box 58)
        - Church on Temple Hofer Field (Box 58)
        - Jewish Synagogue (Box 58)
        - S. Johannis Moabit (Box 58)
      - Expositions (Box 59)
      - Gates (Box 59)
      - Government Buildings (Box 59)
        - Sadhaus (Town Hall) (Box 59)
        - Fire Department (Box 59)
        - Reighs Chancellery (Box 59)
        - Guard House (Box 59)
      - Hospitals (Box 59)
      - Hotels (Box 59)
      - Houses (Box 59)
      - Houses- Apartments (Box 59)
      - Housing (Box 59)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 60)
      - Museums (Box 60)
        - Kraise Fried-Rich Museum (Box 60)
        - Old Museum (Altes Museum) (Box 60)
      - Office Buildings (Box 60)
      - Palaces (Box 60)
      - Restaurants (Box 60)
      - Schools (Box 60)
      - Stadiums (Box 60)
      - Stations (Box 60)
      - Stores (Box 60)
      - Theaters (Box 60)
        - Cinema Lichtburg (Box 61)
        - Grosses Schauspielhaus (Box 61)
        - "Die Komode" Theater (Box 61)
        - Philharmonics Hall (Box 61)
        - Royal Theater (Schauspielhaus) (Box 61)
        - Theater on Kurfurstendam (Box 61)
      - Warehouses (Box 61)
      - Zoos (Box 61)
    - Bingen on the Rhine (Box 61)
    - Birnau (Box 61)
    - Bischofsheim (Box 61)
    - Bonn (Box 61)
    - Bremen (Box 61)
    - Breslau (Box 61)
    - Cannstadt (Box 61)
    - Cassel (Box 61)
    - Castle Antonin (Box 61)
    - Celle (Box 61)
    - Chemnitz (Box 61)
    - Cleve (Box 61)
    - Cologne (Box 61)
      - Bridges (Box 61)
      - Churches (Box 61)
        - S. Elisabeth (Box 61)
        - Steel Evangelical (Box 61)
      - Exhibitions (Box 62)
        - Werkbund Exhibition 1914 (Box 62)
      - Government Buildings (Box 62)
      - Restaurants (Box 62)
      - Stores (Box 62)
    - Cologne-Kalk (Box 62)
    - Dahlem (Box 62)
    - Darmstadt (Box 62)
    - Delstern (Box 62)
    - Dessau (Box 62)
      - Houses (Box 62)
        - Gropius House (Box 62)
      - Housing (Box 62)
        - Torten Siedlung (Box 62)
      - Office Buildings (Box 62)
      - Schools (Box 62)
        - Bauhaus (Box 62)
    - Dresden (Box 62)
      - Banks (Box 62)
      - Prisons (Box 63)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 63)
      - Theaters (Box 63)
    - Dusseldorf (Box 63)
    - Essen (Box 63)
      - Churches (Box 63)
      - Housing (Box 63)
    - Frankfurt (Box 63)
      - Churches (Box 63)
        - Various (Box 63)
        - Frauenfriedens Church (Box 63)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 63)
      - Housing (Box 63)
        - Gas Works (Box 63)
      - Market Buildings (Box 63)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 63)
      - Restaurants (Box 64)
      - Schools (Box 64)
    - Garkau (Box 64)
    - Gelsenkirche (Box 64)
    - Gladbach (Box 64)
    - Glienicke (Box 64)
    - Gross-Lichterfeld (Box 64)
    - Guben (Box 64)
    - Hagen (Box 64)
    - Halle (Box 64)
    - Hamburg (Box 64)
      - Churches (Box 64)
      - Crematories (Box 64)
      - Government Buildings (Box 64)
      - Harbors & Docks (Box 64)
      - Monuments (Box 64)
      - Office Buildings (Box 64)
        - Chilehaus (Box 64)
        - Montanhof (Box 64)
        - Schnellhaus (Box 64)
        - Sprinkenhof (Box 64)
        - Thaliahox (Box 64)
      - Parks (Box 64)
      - Railroad Station (Box 64)
    - Hanover (Box 64)
      - Stations (Box 64)
    - Herren-Chiemsee (Box 64)
    - Hindenburg (Box 64)
    - Hochst-am-Main (Box 65)
    - Hohenblick (Box 65)
    - Jena (Box 65)
    - Kamenz (Box 65)
    - Karlsruhe (Box 65)
    - Kassel (Box 65)
    - Kelheim (Box 65)
    - Konigsberg (Box 65)
    - Krefeld (Box 65)
    - Landsberg (Box 65)
    - Leipzig (Box 65)
      - Exhibitions (Box 65)
      - Government Buildings (Box 65)
      - Housing (Box 65)
      - Market Buildings (Box 65)
      - Monuments (Box 65)
      - Railroad Station (Box 65)
      - Theaters (Box 65)
    - Leversbach (Box 65)
    - Lindlar (Box 65)
    - Lotzen (Box 65)
    - Luban (Box 65)
    - Lubeck (Box 65)
    - Luckenwalde (Box 65)
    - Magdeburg (Box 65)
    - Mulheim (Box 65)
    - Munich (Box 65)
      - Various (Box 65)
      - Churches (Box 65)
        - Anstadtskirche (Box 65)
        - Dombauhutte (Box 65)
        - S. Boniface (Box 65)
        - S. Ludwig (Box 65)
        - Maximilian's Church (Box 65)
      - Exhibitions (Box 66)
      - Government Buildings (Box 66)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 66)
      - Libraries (Box 66)
      - Monuments (Box 66)
        - Temple of Honor (Box 66)
      - Museums (Box 66)
        - Deutsches Museums (Box 66)
        - Glyptothek (Box 66)
        - Maximilanium, 1869 (Box 66)
      - Theaters (Box 66)
      - Tombs (Box 66)
        - Tomb of Unknown Soldier (Box 66)
    - Muskau (Box 66)
    - Neubabelsberg (Box 66)
    - Neuschwanstein (Box 66)
    - Norderney (Box 66)
    - Nuremberg (Box 66)
    - Oberhausen (Box 66)
    - Obermenzing (Box 66)
    - Ordensburg (Box 66)
    - Posen (Box 66)
    - Potsdam (Box 66)
      - Palaces (Box 67)
        - Charlottenhof Palace (Box 67)
      - Castles (Box 67)
      - Churches (Box 67)
      - Houses (Box 67)
      - Theaters (Box 67)
      - Towers (Box 67)
        - Einstein Tower (Box 67)
    - Regensburg (Box 67)
    - Ringenberg (Box 67)
    - Rotenburg-Ob-Dertauber (Box 67)
    - Saarbrucken (Box 67)
    - Salzgitter (Box 67)
    - Soest (Box 67)
    - Springer (Box 67)
    - Stuttgart (Box 67)
      - Houses (Box 67)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 67)
      - Housing (Box 67)
        - Weissenhof (Box 67)
      - Monuments (Box 67)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 67)
      - Stores (Box 67)
    - Tannenburg (Box 67)
    - Tilsit (Box 67)
    - Travermunde (Box 67)
    - Trier (Box 68)
    - Ulm (Box 68)
    - Wartburger (Box 68)
    - Weimar (Box 68)
      - Bauhaus (Box 68)
    - Wiesbaden (Box 68)
    - Wilhelmshoe (Box 68)
    - Wismar (Box 68)
    - Worpswede (Box 68)
    - Wurzburg (Box 68)
    - Zittau (Box 68)
- Greece (Box 68)
  - Athens (Box 68)
    - Libraries (Box 68)
    - Museums (Box 68)
    - Palaces (Box 68)
      - University (Box 68)
- Holland (Box 68)
  [Boxes 68-71]
  - Architects (Box 68)
    - Bazel, K.P.C. de (Box 68)
    - Doesburg, Theo van (Box 68)
    - Leusden, W. van (Box 68)
    - Oud J., J.P.b (Box 68)
  - Cities (Box 68)
    - Albasserdam (Box 68)
    - Amsterdam (Box 68)
      - Various (Box 68)
      - Banks (Box 69)
        - Stock Exchange (Box 69)
      - Houses (Box 69)
      - Housing (Box 69)
        - De Dageraad Housing (Box 69)
        - Public Utility (Box 69)
        - Society Housing (Box 69)
        - South City Housing (Box 69)
        - Spaarndammer-Plantsoen H. (Box 69)
        - For "unsociable" (Box 69)
      - Museums (Box 69)
      - Office Buildings (Box 69)
      - Parks (Box 69)
      - Schools (Box 69)
      - Squares (Box 69)
      - Railroad Stations (Box 69)
      - Stores (Box 69)
    - Eindhoven (Box 69)
    - The Hague (Box 69)
      - Houses (Box 69)
      - Museums (Box 69)
      - Office Buildings (Box 69)
        - B.I.M. Buildings (Box 69)
      - Palaces (Box 70)
        - Palaces (Box 70)
      - Schools (Box 70)
      - Stores (Box 70)
    - Hilversum (Box 70)
      - Bathing Establishment (Box 70)
      - Crematories (Box 70)
      - City Hall (Box 70)
      - Hospitals (Box 70)
      - Hotels (Box 70)
      - Schools (Box 70)
    - Huis-ter-Heide (Box 70)
    - Katwijk-aan-Zee (Box 70)
    - Loodsdrecht (Box 70)
    - Nord Wijkerhout (Box 70)
    - Rotterdam (Box 70)
      - Banks (Box 70)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 70)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 70)
      - Museums (Box 71)
      - Office Buildings (Box 71)
      - Restaurants (Box 71)
      - Schools (Box 71)
      - Stores (Box 71)
    - Schiedam (Box 71)
    - Utrecht (Box 71)
    - Velp (Box 71)
- Hungary (Box 71)
  - Budapest (Box 71)
- India (Box 71)
  - Allahabad (Box 71)
  - Ahmedabad (Box 71)
  - Bombay (Box 71)
  - Chandigarh (Box 71)
    - Various (Box 71)
    - Assembly (Parliament) (Box 72)
    - High Court Building (Box 72)
    - Secretariat (Box 72)
  - New Delhi (Box 72)
    - Council Chamber (Box 72)
    - Secretariat (Box 72)
    - Viceroy's House (Box 72)
  - Nianital (Box 72)
- Iraq (Box 72)
  - Various (Box 72)
- Israel (Box 72)
  - Various (Box 72)
  - Haifa (Box 72)
- Italy (Box 72)
  [Boxes 72-81]
  - General (Box 72)
  - Agriculture (Box 72)
  - Landscapes (Box 72)
  - Architects (Box 73)
    - Antolini, G.A. (Box 73)
    - Brasini, Armando (Box 73)
    - Chiattone, Mario (Box 73)
    - D'Aronco, R. (Box 73)
    - De Giorgio (Box 73)
    - Della Santa, L. (Box 73)
    - De Renzi, Mario (Box 73)
      Xx Architecture 19th-20th c. Belgium, Brussels: Universal Exposition, 1935 Pavilion of Littorio
    - Libera, A. (Box 73)
    - Nervi, Pier Luigi (Box 73)
    - Rusca, Luigi (Box 73)
    - Sant'elia, Antonio (Box 73)
    - Sommaruga, G. (Box 73)
  - Cities (Box 73)
    - Ancona (Box 73)
    - Asti (Box 74)
    - Bergamo (Box 74)
    - Bologna (Box 74)
    - Brescia (Box 74)
    - Brunate (Box 74)
    - Busto Arsizio (Box 74)
    - Cagliari (Box 74)
    - Como (Box 74)
    - Crespi D'Adda (Box 74)
    - Fiesole (Box 74)
    - Florence (Box 74)
      - General Views (Box 74)
        - Maps & Plans (Box 74)
        - Air Views (Box 74)
        - Scoppio Del Carro (Easter) (Box 74)
        - Flood, 1966 (Box 74)
        - Streets (Box 74)
      - Cemeteries (Box 74)
      - Churches (Box 75)
      - Houses (Box 75)
      - Libraries (Box 75)
      - Monuments (Box 75)
      - Palaces (Box 75)
      - Stations (Box 75)
      - Schools (Box 75)
      - Squares (Box 75)
      - Stadiums (Box 75)
      - Villas (Box 75)
    - Gaesta (Box 75)
    - Genoa (Box 75)
    - Genzano (Box 75)
    - Grosseto (Box 75)
    - Gubbio (Box 75)
    - Lake Garda (Box 75)
    - Littoria (Box 75)
    - Livorno (Box 75)
    - Lombardy (Box 75)
    - Matera (Box 75)
    - Milan (Box 75)
      - Various (Box 75)
      - Arches (Box 76)
      - Banks (Box 76)
      - Churches (Box 76)
      - Exhibitions (Box 76)
      - Gates (Box 76)
      - Houses (Box 76)
      - Housing (Box 76)
      - Monuments (Box 76)
      - Monuments (Box 76)
      - Palaces (Box 76)
      - Stations (Box 77)
      - Stores (Box 77)
        - Galerie Emmanuel (Box 77)
      - Squares (Box 77)
      - Theaters (Box 77)
    - Monte Grappa (Box 77)
    - Montepulciano (Box 77)
    - Naples (Box 77)
      - Banks (Box 77)
      - Churches (Box 77)
      - Government Buildings (Box 77)
      - Squares (Box 77)
      - Stations (Box 77)
      - Stores (Box 77)
      - Theaters (Box 77)
        - San Carlo Opera House (Box 77)
    - Orta (Box 77)
    - Padua (Box 77)
    - Palermo (Box 77)
    - Pisa (Box 77)
    - Pordenone (Box 77)
    - Possagno (Box 77)
    - Rome (Box 77)
      - General (Box 77)
        - Maps (Box 77)
      - General Planning (Box 77)
      - General Views (Box 77)
        - Air Views (Box 77)
        - Air Distant (Box 78)
        - Streets (Box 78)
      - Churches (Box 78)
      - Exhibitions (Box 78)
        - E.U.R, 1942 Universal Exposition) (Box 78)
      - Gates (Box 78)
      - Government Buildings (Box 78)
        - Marine Ministry (Box 78)
        - Ministry of Education (Box 78)
        - Ministry of Finance (Box 78)
        - Ministry of Grazia & Giustizia (Box 78)
        - Palace of Justice (Box 78)
      - Hospitals (Box 79)
      - Houses (Box 79)
      - Housing (Box 79)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 79)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 79)
      - Monuments (Box 79)
        - Victor Emmanuel Monument (Box 79)
        - Ardeatine Cave (Box 79)
      - Museums (Box 79)
      - Office Buildings (Box 79)
      - Palaces (Box 79)
      - Schools (Box 79)
        - University of Rome (Box 79)
      - Squares (Box 79)
        - Mussolini Forum (Box 79)
      - Stadiums (Box 79)
        - Palazzette dello Sport (Box 79)
      - Stations (Box 80)
      - Stores (Box 80)
      - Theaters (Box 80)
      - Vatican (Box 80)
      - Villas (Box 80)
    - Sabaudia (Box 80)
    - Sabaudia (Box 80)
    - Settigano (Box 80)
    - Siena (Box 80)
    - Tivoli (Box 80)
    - Todi (Box 80)
    - Trent (Box 80)
    - Trieste (Box 80)
    - Trieste (Box 80)
      - Churches (Box 80)
      - Exhibitions (Box 80)
        - Exhibitions 1902 (Box 80)
        - 1939 (Box 80)
        - 1950 Exhibition Hall (Box 80)
        - 1961 Palace of Labor (Box 81)
      - Government Buildings (Box 81)
        - Facist Group Building, 1940 (Box 81)
      - Housing (Box 81)
      - Industrial Building (Box 81)
        - Automobile Factory (Box 81)
      - Monuments (Box 81)
      - Squares (Box 81)
      - Stadiums (Box 81)
      - Theaters (Box 81)
      - Villas (Box 81)
    - Udine (Box 81)
    - Vallombrosa (Box 81)
    - Varese (Box 81)
    - Venice (Box 81)
      - Canals (Box 81)
      - Palaces (Box 81)
      - Squares (Box 81)
    - Vinci (Box 81)
- Japan (Box 81)
  - Kagawa (Box 81)
  - Kamakuba (Box 81)
  - Kobe (Box 81)
  - Kofu (Box 81)
  - Miyakonojo (Box 81)
  - Nakasendo (Box 81)
  - Shizvoka (Box 81)
  - Tokyo (Box 81)
    - Various (Box 81)
    - Imperial Hotel (Box 81)
    - Mitsui Bank (Box 82)
    - Mitsui Bank (Box 82)
    - Parliament (Box 82)
- Parliament (Box 82)
  - Montecarlo (Box 82)
- Norway (Box 82)
  - Oslo (Box 82)
  - Tromso (Box 82)
- Philippines (Box 82)
  - Various (Box 82)
- Poland (Box 82)
  - Various (Box 82)
- Portugal (Box 82)
  - Cintra (Box 82)
- Russia (Box 82)
  [Boxes 82-86]
  - General (Box 82)
    - Various (Box 82)
  - Architects (Box 82)
    - Alexander, L.C. (Box 82)
    - Birkenberg (Box 82)
    - Bocharov, M. (Box 82)
    - Fomin (Box 82)
    - Hartmann (Box 82)
    - Helfreich, V.G. (Box 82)
      Xx Schouko
    - Ladovsky, N. (Box 82)
    - Lenpromstroiproekt (Box 82)
    - Lissitzky, El (Box 82)
    - Mavelich, K. (Box 82)
      Xx for drawings of Architecture, see Sculpture Russia, Malevich
    - Mardvinov, A.G. (Box 83)
    - Rojine, I.E. (Box 83)
    - Schouko, V.A. (Box 83)
    - Schoussev, A.V. (Box 83)
    - Teplistsky (Box 83)
    - Velikanov (Box 83)
      Xx Fomin
    - Vesnin, Alexander (Box 83)
    - Voronikin, A.N. (Box 83)
  - Cities (Box 83)
    - Baku (Box 83)
    - Berezovi Nabolok (Arcangel) (Box 83)
    - Gorki (Box 83)
    - Gorlovka (Box 83)
    - Gruzina (Box 83)
    - Iaroslavl (Box 83)
    - Irkutska (Box 83)
    - Kazan (Box 83)
    - Kem (Box 83)
    - Kharkov (Box 83)
    - Kiev (Box 83)
    - Kirejevo (Box 83)
    - Kronstadt (Box 83)
    - Leningrad (Box 83)
      - Various (Box 83)
      - Banks (Box 83)
        - Exchanges (Box 83)
      - Bridges (Box 83)
      - Churches (Box 83)
        - Resurrection Church (Box 83)
        - Transfiguration Cathedral (Box 83)
        - Trinity Cathedral (Box 83)
      - Convents (Box 83)
      - Government Buildings (Box 83)
        - Various (Box 83)
        - Admiralty (Box 83)
        - German Embassy (Box 84)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 84)
      - Libraries (Box 84)
      - Museums (Box 84)
      - Palaces (Box 84)
      - Schools (Box 84)
      - Theaters (Box 84)
    - Magnitogorsk (Box 84)
    - Maineft (Box 84)
    - Moscow (Box 84)
      - Banks (Box 84)
      - Churches (Box 84)
      - Clubs (Box 84)
      - Government Buildings (Box 84)